babynology.com 2005-12-12

# Privacy Statement - Babynology.com

Baby names with meaning, boy names, girl names, male , female, mean, words, kids stuff, resources, directory, fun stuff, free games, photo contest, men woman, Australian, Buddhist, Dutch, English, French, German, Greek, Hebrew, Hindu, Iranian, Irish, child, children, Baby names, boys names girls names for African, American, Anglo, Arabic, Italian, Japanese, Latin, Malaysian, Muslim, Parsi, Portuguese, Tamil, name with meaning

|    
|   
---  

**Privacy Statement**

Babynology takes users privacy seriously and we ensuring that your privacy is respected and protected. Your are free to use our web site with directly providing any of your information. For more details on our Privacy Policy please read below :

Third Party Advertising - We use third-party advertising to serve ads on our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

Information We Collect and What We Do With It

Advertiser and Partner Links - Babynology contains links to advertiser and partner websites. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such non-Babynology websites, and we do not control the practices of any of our advertisers or partners to whom we are linked. In order to participate in certain partner and/or advertiser supplied services and tools you may be required to provide personally identifiable information to the advertisers and partners whose tools and services you have chosen to interact with. Each advertiser and partner may request different information from you. If you have additional questions about how one of our advertisers, partners or sponsors use information about you, we urge you to contact them directly. 

Third Party Cookies - In the course of serving advertisements to this site and tracking of hits, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

Cookies - Our site uses a feature of your browser to set a "cookie" on your computer. Babynology can then read the cookies whenever you visit the Babynology websites. We use cookies to track the pages you've visited and to make sure you don't see the same ads repeatedly. You may modify your browser preference to provide you with choices relating to cookies. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies you may be unable to use those Babynology services that require registration. 

Contact - If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or anything else about Babynology, Contact us.  

|
